Here is your power, from whom
Вот ваша власть у кого
the man steals, here is you, from whom he steals,
ворует мужчина вот вам са у кого ворует
your
ваша
power is stolen by
власть воруют
everyone Hello Hello, I’m from the city of
все Здраствуй Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsk Where are you from? I’m from Krasnoyarsk and
Хмельницке Вы откуда Я из Красноярска а
what are you communicating here? Well, you
чём общаетесь тут ну вы же Сами
yourself probably understand about
понимаете наверно сами об убийстве
Navalny’s murder and how you
Навального понял да как вы
killed him, here I am  I’m asking you, are you as a
его убил вот я вас спрашиваю вы как
Russian person from Russia yes, what do you
русский человек из России да Как вы
think about Well, let’s think together
думаете к Ну давайте вместе подумаем
let’s I think
давайте я думаю
Putin Well, look, this is your opinion
Путин Ну вот смотрите это ваше мнение
correctly Yes wa Can I s Well, well, I kind of,
правильно Да ва Можно я с Ну ну я у меня
well, maybe he, in principle, died himself
как бы ну может он в принципе сам умер
Well Well, quickly  there’s nothing at all So, well,
Ну Ну скорее всего нет Так так ну
look, for example, this Navalny was already in
смотрите например вот этот Навальный уже
prison, he was still in prison for 9 years And he was
сидел уже ему 9 лет ещё сидеть было И
sitting somewhere in the Arctic Circle,
сидел где-то за полярным кругом про него
absolutely everyone forgot about him
забыли абсолютно все
Well, at least Russian society
Ну по крайней мере российское общество
forgot about him for sure, yeah, he was sitting Well,
про него забыло точно угу вот сидел Ну
you know, he’s always in  look for someone who
вот понимаете всегда в каком-то ищи кому
benefits you know what it is who benefits yes
выгодно знаете что такое кому выгодно да
yes You yourself said looking for someone that
да Вот Вы же сами сказали ищ кому то
is, well, roughly speaking, I don’t believe that it
есть ну грубо говоря я не верю чтобы
would be beneficial for Putin to kill him, why is
Путину было выгодно его убить зачем Вот
he sitting there about
он сидит о
even worthless forgot Biden Trump Who killed I
ещё негоже забыли байден Трамп Кто убил
have no idea  yes, look,
поняти не имею а есть ну смотрите вот у
I have an idea, just like according to
меня есть понятие как раз как по
official data, her Trom
официальным данным у неё Тром
was blown up, as if it were possible No, to be honest,
подорвался как бы возможно Нет ну честно
x knows him, well, well, Putin It
говоря х его знает ну ну ну Путину Это
was definitely not profitable to
точно было невыгодно его
kill him Why is he sitting there anyway? They forgot about him,
убивать Зачем он и так сидит про него
why
забыли зачем его
kill him Well  just with my head that's
убивать Ну вот просто головой вот
bare who then who killed him I have no idea
голо кто тогда кто его убил Понятия не
again I say I have no data I do
имею опять же говорю у меня нету данных
n't have I have an assumption
У меня нет у меня есть предположение
guess Say guess yes
предположение Скажите предположение да
yes guess
да предположение
Say well I guess that
Скажите ну я предполагаю что это это
someone did it and well agents of the West agents of the
сделал кто-то и ну агенты Запада агенты
West  that is, agents of the West in a
Запада то есть агенты запада в
Russian prison, such a
Российской тюрьме приехал такой
black Vars Neger arrived, some kind of black man, why
чернокожий Варс негер какой-то почему бы
not, why not someone paid
нет почему бы нет кому-то заплатили
someone, gave money to him, injected him with something and
кому-то дали денег что-то ему вколол и
everything is cool,
всё
easy, all this is done,
прикольно легко всё это делается
done easily and why raise it
делается легко и зачем поднять Вот
Now I’m buoy  be indignant And although she, in
сейчас бую негодовать А хотя она в
principle, will not rise up against this
принципе не поднимется на этого
Navalny, in general, no one gave a [ __ ] that in
Навального вообще всем было похуй что в
Russia, that for some reason, well, the West simply does not
России что почему-то ну просто Запад не
understand the Russian mentality, that
понимает российский менталитет что на на
Navalny doesn’t give a damn, no one gives a damn about him.
Навального насрать всем на него насрать
You see, when he was sent from
Понимаете когда его отправляли из
Germany to Russia, he
Германии в Россию он же прекрасно
understood perfectly well  that he will come here and sit down
понимал что он приедет сюда и сядет
and nevertheless went, I understood, I’m a pony, I
и тем не менее поехал понял я я пони я
understand correctly
правильно понимаю
that no one gives a [ __ ] about Navalny so much
что всем настолько насрать на Навального
that you’ve already been for 10 minutes. So you’ve been justifying
что вы уже 10 минуто Так оправдываете
why no one gives a [ __ ] about Navalny. Yes, yes,
почему всем насрать на Навального Да да
I’m just with you, you asked me a question,
я просто с вами вы мне задали вопрос да
yes, but you  so you are so zealously trying to prove
да но вы так вы так рьяно доказываете
that Navalny is not interesting to anyone, just
что Навальный никому не интересен прям
not in Russia, in fact, I am not
стоко нет в Россию на самом деле мне он
interested in him in Russia, he is not interesting to
не интересен в России не интересен
anyone, he really is not interesting,
никому он правда не интересен
you know what happened to him in the last six months, I do
знаете что последние полгода с ним
n’t even have an interest in this, yeah, I
этом не имею даже интересовался Ага
understand, where are you from then?  now if you are
понял А откуда вы тогда вот если он вам
not interested in him How did you know that he
не интересен Откуда вы узнали что он
died news The first column now now
умер новости Первая колонка сейчас
the news
теперь новостях
goes like this if no one is interested in him
идт так если он никому не интересен
Why why if no one is
Почему почему если он никому не
interested in him why is he in all the
интересен почему он во всех колонках
news columns then if he is neither
новостей тогда если он ни
us And
мы А
who the news columns create the Western
кто колонки новостей создают Западный
mainstream  If you didn’t know in the
мейнстрим Если вы не знали а в
Russian
российских
media, you will understand that he creates the Western mainstream. The same is true for
СМИ вы поймите что Западный мейнстрим он
our news, that
создаёт Точно также и и наши новости то
is, what is the main thing for them is also the
есть что у них на главно то и у нас
main thing for us. That is, for example,
появляется на главно То есть например
Simonyan Skabeeva. They look at what is the
Симонян скабеева Они смотрят что у
main thing for the West and they themselves start  this is
запада на главно и сами начинают это
to tell
рассказывать
Yes no They tell every day
Да нет Они каждый день рассказывают
That is, I understand correctly that the
То есть я правильно понимаю что
Russian media do not have their own news,
российские СМИ они своих новостей не
they just copy the
имеют они копируют просто
Western ones, not always and not a fact, well, you
западные не всегда и не фак ну вы же
said that they kind of take and copy the Western.
сказали что они типа берут и Западное
I said that, in principle, the
копируют Я сказал что в принципе у
West has a lot  resources to create a
Запада очень много ресурсов создавать
mainstream like this Well, the Russians there are
мейнстрим так Ну а российские там
Skobeeva Solovyov, then why are they
скобеева Соловьёв они тогда зачем это
writing this if no one is interested in him? In
пишут если он никому не интересен в
Russia this is for internal use.
России это для внутреннего пользования
What does it mean for internal
Что значит для внутреннего
use Skobeeva and Solovyov? These
пользования скобеева и Соловьёв это Эти
people are for internal use, that is,
люди для внутреннего пользования то есть
they use you Yes,
они вами пользуются Да
inside it turns out yes yes  that is, they
внутри получается да да то есть они
enter your
заходят в ваш
inner circle, they create the same mainstream,
вну они создают мейнстрим тот же самый
again in Russia. That is, I
опять же России То есть я правильно
understand Solovyov correctly. Yes, it
понимаю Соловьёв Да очень информационно
goes deep into every person in a very informative way and
заходит вглубь каждого человека и
uses it, and
пользуется этим да
look, recently there was an interview between
смотрите вот недавно вот было интервью
Carlson and Putin,
Карлсона с Путиным
and Skabeeva’s words with this with gusto
да и скабеевой словв с этим с упоением
they talked about it
об этом рассказывали
correctly. Well, not only did Skobeeva
правильно Ну там не только скобеева там
become famous all over the world, but
на весь мир прославился но тем не
nevertheless, they
ме они пось его
tell the whole country using his name. Why does
именем рассказывают на всю страну Зачем
Skobeeva
скобеева на внутренний пользование
talk about Navalny for internal use if
рассказывает про Навального если он
no one is interested in him within the
никому не интересен внутри
country, inside the country he is not interested, but
страны внутри неинтересен но тем не
nevertheless, since this
менее так как это
enters the mainstream of the West, so
входит в мейнстрим Запада соответственно
she tells Yes, why is Skobeeva
она и рассказывает Да у Зачем скобеева
talking about the mainstream of the
рассказывает про мейнстрим
West? You want her to remain silent
Запада Вы хотите чтобы она промолчала
if no one is interested in him, why
так если он никому не интересен зачем
tell him he’s not interested, but
рассказывать не интересен но тем не
nevertheless, everyone knows him, he was such a
менее это все его знают он был такой
person, you know, he died,
человек вот ли знат Вот вот умер
he broke away
оторвался
trope is not like this for anyone And why does
троп никому не так так А из-за чего его
everyone know him if no one is
все знают если он никому не
interested in him Probably because he him
интересен Наверное потому что ему ему
him his name made the right name
ему ему имя сделал запит правильно имя А
What does it mean made a name made a name it
что означает сделал имя сделал имя это
means that his name is interesting to someone and
значит что его имя кому-то интересно да
some  people
какие-то люди
even predicted him in the Orange Revolution, the
его даже прочили в оранжевой Революции
future
будущий
president, how do Russians know about
президент откуда россияне знают про
Navalny if they are not
Навального если он им не интересен
seriously interested in him Yes, from a tube, that is, they watch
серьёзно Да из туба то есть они смотрят
his YouTube Navalny is not interesting to them But
его YouTube Навальный не интересен им Но
they watch Navalny’s YouTube Well, well,
они смотрят YouTube Навального Да ну у
I also watched Navalny’s YouTube, then
я тоже смотрел YouTube Навального дальше
it means he  you were
значит он тебе был
only interested in how, let’s say,
интересен только как э скажем
some small alternative, but
так какая-то небольшая альтернатива но
no more, no more, look and you Well,
не больше не более того смотри а ты Ну
let’s do it Well, we are adults How
давай так Ну мы же взрослые люди Как
often have you watched
часто ты посматривал YouTube
Navalny’s YouTube I often watch
Навального я я часто смотрю YouTube
Nightingale’s YouTube nene But Navalny’s YouTube
соловья нене А вот Навального YouTube
how often have you  I didn’t watch it often at all,
как часто ты посматривал вообще не часто
well, I probably saw a couple of his videos all the time. Did
ну я всё время может пару видео его
you watch it yourself or with your
видел пару видео А ты сам смотрел или с
wife, for example, watched the tube together, wife?
женой например вместе смотрели тубе жена
Well, you watched Navalny’s YouTube from your wife.
Ну ты в тихаря от жены смотрел YouTube
What does it mean in quiet, well, you
Навального Что значит в тихаря ну ты сам
watched it yourself so that no one saw under the
смотрел чтобы никто не увидел под
pillow  the [ __ ] was hiding or something Well, I don’t
подушкой [__] скрывался что ли Ну я не
know Yes, that’s how I just don’t know how
знаю Да вот как я просто не знаю как
people watch Navalny’s YouTube
люди смотрят YouTube Навального Вот
Just like I’m talking to
точно так же как сейчас разговариваю с
you now, I’ll want to watch something, I’ll watch it
тобой вот захочу что-нибудь посмотреть
Well, I’ll take a look, I’ll draw conclusions for myself, it’s
посмотрю Ну посмотрю сделаю для себя
all like this, I mean, you
выводы всё вот так вот приме То есть вы
they sat down not with their family Well, like, so that
сами сели не с семьёй Ну типа так чтобы
the neighbors don’t know, I’d use Navalny’s family
соседи не знали буду б семьёй Навального
to watch Well, it’s right
смотреть Ну правильно бли Навального
to watch Navalny with my family But
смотреть с семьёй Но это ну
damn, this is such a spectacle, the wife will say Hey,
блин это так себе зрелище жена скажет Эй
what are you watching
ты что смотришь
Navalny Pervert,
Навального Извращенец
but not she will say Hey, you’re
да не она скажет Эй ты сейчас
busy
занялся тебе
doing it for you now  I understand And look,
делать понял А смотрите
here she is, she’s on the spit of all these
вот вот она коху на вертела всех этих
bulk ones I understand What your wife’s name is, it doesn’t matter, it doesn’t matter, it’s a cool name,
навальных понял А как вашу жену
it doesn’t matter why I’ll tell you what
неважно зачем я буду тебе говорить как
My wife’s name is, what your wife’s name is, my
Мою жену зовут как твою жену зовут мою
wife’s name is Svetlana
жену Светлана
Stepanovna Very nice But I’ll still
Степановна Очень приятно Но я всё-таки
keep it a secret  The name of my wife, yeah, so
оставлю в тайне Имя моей жены угу так
the question is, I can tell you what my name is, it’s
вопрос могу сказать как меня зовут это
no problem What’s your name Well,
без проблем Как вас зовут Ну а жену
let’s leave my wife For sko Let’s My
Давайте оставлю За ско Давайте Меня
name is Vasily Petrovich What is your name, what is my
зовут Василий Петрович Вас как зовут
Ukrainian
украинское
name What is your name Sergey
имя меня какое Как вас зовут Сергей
Sergeyevich My name is
Сергей евич Меня зовут
Sergeyevich Sergey Evgenievich Sergeyevich
Сергеевич Сергей Евгеньевич Сергей евич
yes  sir Sergey Evich Yes, okay Sergey
дае сер Сергей евич Да хорошо Сергей
Evich look Did you look at
евич смотрите А вы посматривали ютубчик
Navalny’s YouTube during the day in the evening at night when it
Навального днём вечером ночью когда это
was I don’t even remember when I did it I understood
было даже не помн ког делал понял
what you can
а какие можете можете
tell you can tell your
рассказать можете рассказать свои
feelings after watching
ощущения после просмотра ютубчик
Navalny’s YouTube I can
Навального могу
Let’s have another Western bot Western
Давайте очередной Западный бот Западный
bot understood of course without
бот понял конечно без
options but  he came to see you in Krasnoyarsk,
вариантов а он к вам в Красноярск
maybe he came, I didn’t see him
приезжал может приезжал я его не видел
in person Well, you didn’t think I can’t even say
лично Ну а вы не думали Даже сказать не
he wasn’t interesting to me I
могу он мне был не интересен Я как-то
was once about the promoted videos there, his
было про раскрученные видео там у него
exposure there about Putin’s
разоблачение там на счёт путинского
palace, something like that was me  somehow Gra
дворца что-то такое было я как-то Гра
eyes, well, a couple of Videos I watched
глаза вот ну пару Видео я посмотрел
True Well, I’m just answering honestly, look
Правда Ну я просто честно отвечаю смотри
And if at work you found out that you were
А если бы на работе узнали что вы вот
watching Navalny’s video out of the corner of your eye,
краем глаза но смотрели Навального видео
what would happen and and what, well, you wouldn’t be
что бы было и и что ну вас бы не
judged that well, damn it’s perversion looking
осуждали что ну блин извращение смотрит
there  in quiet Navalny Yes, people don't give a [ __ ] And
там в тихаря Навального Да людям похуй А
who
вы кем
do you work for?
работаете
I'll tell you a senior manager, a
я мы скажем старшего звена менеджер
senior manager in which
старшего звена в какой
area of
сфере продажах
equipment sales in equipment sales, I
оборудования в продажах оборудования
understand. Did you watch the
понял А вы про Навального смотрели
German version or the Russian version about Navalny?
немецкую версию или российскую
Why not the German version, but the
версию Зачем не немецкая версия а
Russian film, he's there, he's the same  a
русский фильм он там он же он же ещё
few years ago he regularly
несколько лет назад он с регулярностью
released films there, there was an
там выпускал фильмы там
anti-corruption committee there, he
антикоррупционный комитет у него там
had something like that there, yes. Well, he
что-то такое было да Ну вот он там
released it there, well, he told something about Putin’s palace,
выпускал там ну про дворец Путина что-то
yes, not interesting,
там рассказывал да да не интересно
boring girls, look Well, I honestly say,
скучно девочки смотри Ну я честно говорю
me too  I’m ashamed to admit, but I
я тоже я мне стыдно признаться но я про
also watched this video about Putin’s palace.
дворец Путина тоже этот видосик
Well, it’s a pretty good
посмотрел Ну довольно довольно
quality video, I would say, you know, I do
качественное видео я бы сказал знаете я
n’t argue with a high-quality video, well
не спорю качественное видео хорошо
made, I don’t argue with a clear fact like that, well, just
сделано не спорю чёткий факта такой ну
yes, just understand, here you see, the World Cup does
просто да да только понимаете тут видите
n’t fit in at all.
вчм не вже не вяжется
That’s who it is  Putin and why does he need a
Вот кто есть Путин и зачем ему
palace? I wonder why everyone here
дворец интересно зачем всем вот этим
had palaces, but no Dodika, it’s
додика дворцы были да нет додика то
clear, but you understand that Putin exists.
понятно но вы понимаете что есть Путин
He is that Putin is a tsar, essentially a tsar, and what kind of a
Он что есть Путин царь по сути царь а
tsar without a
что за царь без
palace is this palace could be registered in the name of
дворца это дворец оформить можно было на
anyone
любого
else, so that’s
другого так это ж
it  Well, that’s what Navalny said, it’s
это Это ж Навальный это и говорил то он
registered to dummies. Well, it’s from
оформлен на подставных лиц Да ну это с
your taxes to serve Putin,
ваших налогов для обслуживания Путина
in short, this is a palace, he said that for
короче это дворец он же это и говорил
God’s sake. Yes, for God’s sake, the authorities have always
ради Бога Да за ради Бога власть всегда
stolen and will steal here in general here.
воровала и будет воровать тут вообще тут
I understand in any
Поня в любой
direction who the power is
строне кого власть
stealing Now, what flag are you under? Well, the
ворует Вот вы сейчас под каким флагом ну
Russian government is
Российская власть у кого
not stealing from whom. Here is your power, from whom is
ворует не Вот ваша власть у кого
the man stealing, from whom is it
ворует мужчина вот вам само у кого
stealing? Your
ворует ваша
power is being stolen by all the officials in ponies. I have a
власть воруют все чиновники во пони я
question: Who is your power stealing from?
вопрос У кого Вот ваша власть ворует раз
And from whom is your power stealing?  budget
все А у кого ваша власть ворует бюджета
from the people from the people That is, from you, of course,
у народа у народа То есть у вас конечно
and from your wife, I
и у вашей жены
understood from them that she steals a lot of pain,
же понял у них она ворует гораздо боль
you normally perceive that your
вы нормально воспринимаете что ваша
power
власть у
is yours. Is it that now I have discovered the secret that the
вас это Это что сейчас открыл секрет что
government in any country always steals? I
власть в любой стране всегда ворует Я
’m asking for you, is it normal that yours
спрашиваю для вас нормально что ваша
power steals know this absolutely
власть ворует знать это абсолютно потому
because it has always been like this and for
что это всегда было так как и для
corruption this is not corruption neni inig
коррупция это не корупция нени иниг
Crown on the head on the head this is more
Корона на головой на голове вот это
important dumbfounded ppi on Tsey reserve
важливе оголошення ппи на Цей резервний
channel Andr Popik chatroulette I created
канал Андр Попик чатрулетка я створив ще
another channel on which I put unique
один канал на який вкладаю уникальни
video I didn’t boo  neither on any channel nor on
вдео я не були ни на цьому канали ни на
streams write on any day they
стримах пишиться на нього там кожен день
will appear New and but video squeak
будуть виходити Нови и но вдео писка
comment PD for every video video to YouTube yogo
комент ПД кожним вдео щоб YouTube його
effektivni prova mi vinni collapse that
ефективни прова ми повинни рухну той
channel so that more people
канал для того щоб бильше людей
can get information from our videos that's
отримували информацию з наших вдео тому
what Our channel Yes  troshka YouTube having driven a
що це Наш канал Да трошки YouTube загнав
new ban, we will try more in parallel
ньй бан мы будем пробу ще паралельно ро
write one
один пиши